(Howard:)of this award-winning minivan.
(Bernadette:)Fine, we'll go to the E.R.
Just stop selling me on the van.
(Howard:)You're right. It sells itself.
(Raj:)You have to admit,
it's a pretty smooth ride.
(Bernadette:)I was hoping it'd be quieter.
(Howard:)If childbirth is half this bad,
you are so screwed!
Are we there yet?!
Soon.
Why is it taking so long?!
H-Howard, Howard,
look at the DVD screen.
I put on Batman: The Animated
Series. Your favorite!
(Howard:)I'm in too much pain
to watch cartoo...
Oh! This is a good one.
(Raj:)I've been babysitting him
(Raj:)way longer than you have.
(Bernadette:)Fine. I'll buy the stupid van.
(Bert:)This is the best blintz
I've ever had.
(Sheldon:)Oh. Thank you.
(Bert:)It almost makes up for the
incredibly awkward turn
(Bert:)things took earlier.
(Amy:)You know what,
I-I think I'm just gonna go.
(Amy:)No, Stuart, don't.
No, I-I consider you
and Sheldon like my family,